<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>MetalBlueberry</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on MetalBlueberry</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Víctor Pérez Domingo</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Posts</title>
      <link>/post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/</guid>
      <description></description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Any fool can write code that a computer can understand. Good programmers write code that humans can understand.
 Martin Fowler, 2008.   About MetalBlueberry 
I&amp;rsquo;m a passionate developer with experience working on critical real time environments like payments and bank transfers.
I have more than 4 years of experience writing highly scalable systems with Go and I consider this my main area of expertise. I also feel comfortable with other languages, such as Python and Javascript.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me - The long story</title>
      <link>/the-long-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/the-long-story/</guid>
      <description>About MetalBlueberry I&amp;rsquo;m a programmer since I discovered that things could be automated.
Attention
You are about to read my life since I remember it, focused on how I became a professional developer.  The beginning I started with Win-logo in the school by drawing some figures with simple functions. I still remember what could be one of the firsts method I&amp;rsquo;ve ever written. tits(size) The objective is clear, draw two tangent circles of the desired size.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>F.A.Q</title>
      <link>/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/faq/</guid>
      <description>Frequently Asked Questions These are questions that you may want to ask me. I think it is a cool way to get to know each other.
How is your development environment? My operative system is Linux with the Ubuntu distribution. The desktop environment is Regolith which is based on i3wm. I mainly develop on vscode because it is flexible and can be used for almost any language. check out my extensions.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Networks</title>
      <link>/social/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/social/</guid>
      <description>   Víctor Pérez Domingo  Follow @MetalBlueberry   Follow @MetalBlueberry    .centered { display: flex; justify-content: center; flex-direction: column; align-items: center; } </description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
